前头路途险峻又长远
There's a long and winding road ahead
几朵乌云遮住脸
A few black clouds lay over head
而那太阳却总是不见踪影
And the shining sun is nowhere to be seen
但你只要起身继续走
But with every step and fall you take
敢于接受新事物
all your thoughts and leaps of faith
雨过似乎就一定会有天青
There's a silver lining somewhere in between
闭上眼
Close your eyes
深呼吸
Breathe in slow
缓缓吐气
Then let it go
当旅途渐渐变长
Stop and smell the roses
停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
当生命想唱反调
When you feel your life's against you
而让你全身毫无能量
and your energy is gone
并非谁都知道何时
'Cause not everybody knows when
该让自己放个松
it's just time to catch a break
当你累到只想自己静一静时
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
Stop and smell the roses
今天又有了新点子
Today has found another way
想将昨天带回到眼前
to turn right into yesterday
只因时间又再次熄灭了光源
'Cause time has taken all the light again
就算我摆弄著现实
But if I fiddle with reality
想试图改变我的未来
to try and change who I should be
最后还不是仍然呆站在起点
I'm tucking my own destiny in bed
闭上眼
Close your eyes
深呼吸
Breathe in slow
缓缓吐气
Then let it go
当旅途渐渐变长
Stop and smell the roses
停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
当生命想唱反调
When you feel your life's against you
而让你全身毫无能量
and your energy is gone
并非谁都知道何时
'Cause not everybody knows when
该让自己放个松
it's just time to catch a break
当你累到只想自己静一静时
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
当旅途渐渐变长
Stop and smell the roses
停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
when your journey's getting long
当生命想唱反调
When you feel your life's against you
而让你全身毫无能量
and your energy is gone
并非谁都知道何时
'Cause not everybody knows when
该让自己放个松
it's just time to catch a break
当你累到只想自己静一静时
When you're draining
and you just don't wanna show it
停下来闻闻玫瑰花香
Stop and smell the roses